Help on module cur:

NAME
    cur

DESCRIPTION
    Recommender System - CUR decomposition by :
    S.Devendra Dheeraj Gupta  -  2017B5A70670H
    K.Srinivas  -  2017B3A70746H
    Abhirath Singh -  2018A7PS0521H
    Ritvik C -  2018A7PS0180H

    CUR Algorithm:
    Sparse matrix A can be represented as C*U*R where C is a matrix consisting of columns of A and R is a matrix consisting of rows of A.
    C and R are sparse matrices while U is dense.

FUNCTIONS
    RMSE(pred, value)
        RMSE functoin takes the predicted ratings and the actual ratings as parameters
        and returns the RMSE of the predictions as the result.
    
    SpearmanRankCorrelation(mat, predicted)
        spearmanCorr functoin takes the predicted ratings and the actual ratings as parameters
        and returns the spearman correlation of the predictions as the result.
    
    precisionattopk(matrix, pred)
        precisionAtRankK functoin takes the predicted ratings, actual ratings and
        number of ratings as parameters and returns the precision of the predictions as the result.
        A threshold rating of 3 has been used to identify valid predictions.

