Help on module svd:

NAME
    svd

DESCRIPTION
    Recommender System - SVD decomposition by :
    S.Devendra Dheeraj Gupta  -  2017B5A70670H
    K.Srinivas  -  2017B3A70746H
    Abhirath Singh -  2018A7PS0521H
    Ritvik C -  2018A7PS0180H

    Singular value decomposition with 100% energy retention and 90% energy retention
    The sparse matrix A can be represented as:
    A = U*Sigma*V'

FUNCTIONS
    RMSE(pred, value)
        RMSE functoin takes the predicted ratings and the actual ratings as parameters
        and returns the RMSE of the predictions as the result.
    
    precisionattopk(matrix, pred)
        precisionattopk functoin takes the predicted ratings, actual ratings and
        number of ratings as parameters and returns the precision of the predictions as the result.
        A threshold rating of 3 has been used to identify valid predictions.
    
    spearmanCorr(pred, value)
        spearmanCorr functoin takes the predicted ratings and the actual ratings as parameters
        and returns the spearman correlation of the predictions as the result.

